So this is this is clip one and its about how to pick a suitable idea to make a glass mosaic.
I don't know how to explain this except that sometimes ideas just come into my head out of someplace.
Or else I think maybe people would like to see something that's more abstract and I just kinda just have fun with the glass and add other materials to it and so on.
Other times I see pictures of something like I saw a picture of a Beatles on Abbey Road and I though boy that would be neat to do that in glass.
Or pictures of some horses I saw in the paper that were, they had their noses together, looked like they were kissing and I thought that was really sweet.
Or else sometimes I see a picture of horse races like this in the paper.
And I think, boy that would be neat, how could I put that all together in a horse race?
So one of the ways you can get ideas for doing a project like this is to maybe scan over some art books.
There's a lot of art books that are out there and all the old masters and different people or more modern things.
Whatever you might learn.
Or even pictures in the paper.
Anything, a scene you might see, take a photograph of it.
I've done that too.
I've taken photographs of things and used that as a basis.
So those are some of the ways that you can use to start with.